

# CONTACT



(+91) 7478284428



arkya22@gmail.com



Kolkata, West Bengal, India



Bangalore, Karnataka, India



linkedin.com/in/arkyasantra-3bb475175



https://github.com/masc4424



https://rb.gy/yzlzxk

# SKILLS

MS Word, MS Excel & MS Power Point



C,C++,Python & Java



Java Script, HTML, PHP, CSS & SQL



VIDEO EDITING & IMAGE EDITING



# LANGUAGES



HINDI



BENGALI - - -

HOBBIES







# **ARKYA SANTRA**

An enthusiastic Electronics and Communication Engineer with experience in projects based in AI and IoT as well as training in Python, JAVA, C & C++ and also experienced in Web Development in possession of strong communication and leadership skills.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### B. Tech Electronics and Communication. 2018-2022 Adamas University, Kolkata, India

- Member of IETE Kolkata Region.
- Received 2nd prize in Techx 2019 organized by ADAMAS UNIVERSITY.
- Published a paper on "UWB Antenna with Bandwidth Enhancement for 5G, IOT, USB-dongle and UWB Wireless Applications" || Journal named: IEEE Xplore.
- Project: Home automation using Node MCU.
- Project: College Management System Android App and Website.
- Marks: 8.84 CGPA

#### **Higher Secondary Education (10+2)** 2017-2018 Kendriya Vidyalaya, West Bengal, India

- Received 1st Prize in English Spelling Competition
- Marks: 51%

# Secondary Education (10)

2014-2015

# Kendriya Vidyalaya, Tamil Nadu, India

Marks: 6.8 CGPA

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **Student Intern**

Feb 2021-March 2021

# CoreEL Tech., Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

- Successfully completed the internship on Functional Verification using SystemVerilog.
- Completed the Project on Carry Skip adder using System Verilog.

#### Student Intern

July 2021-Aug 2021

## The Sparks Found., Singapore

- Successfully completed the internship on Web Development.
- Completed the Project on making a Basic Banking System.

## Student Intern

June 2021-Aug 2021

## Spotle.AI, Kolkata, India

- Successfully completed the internship on Spotle.ai NASSCOM Community AI.
- Completed the Project on Analyse Crop Production